mathpapa.com 2019-09-25

# Privacy Policy -- MathPapa

The MathPapa web site and any related mobile applications (collectively, the "Service") constitute a hosted service operated by MathPapa, Inc. ("MathPapa"). This Privacy Policy describes how MathPapa collects, uses, discloses and secures information collected from or about you and your devices through the Service. By using the Service you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, you may not use the Services. MathPapa may update this Privacy Policy from time-to-time in our sole discretion in accordance with the modification provision of the Terms and Conditions of Use. Your use of the Service following us posting a new Privacy Policy on the Service signifies that you agree to and accept the Privacy Policy as modified pursuant to the "Modifications of Terms" section of the Terms of Use.

This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by the Service and how it is used and disclosed. 

### Log Files

The Service makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), anonymous identifiers, date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, text inputs, and clicks to analyze trends, administer the Service, track users movement around the Service, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such anonymous identifiers are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to MathPapa's Service choose to interact with MathPapa in ways that require MathPapa to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that MathPapa gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at MathPapa to provide a username, date of birth, and email address. Those who engage in financial transactions with MathPapa are asked to provide additional information, such as name and credit card number. In each case, MathPapa collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with MathPapa. MathPapa does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. Visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

When you download and use our Service, we automatically collect information on the type of device you use, operating system version, and the device identifier (or "UDID"). 

### Analytics

We perform analytics for internal use to improve our design and features. We do this ourselves and through third party providers, including [Google Analytics](https://www.google.com/analytics/), [Mixpanel](https://www.mixpanel.com/), [Segment](https://www.segment.com/), and [ProfitWell](https://www.profitwell.com/). 

### Mobile Analytics

We do not collect personally identifiable information, such as first and last name, address, or email, when you first download our Mobile App. We collect persistent identifiers from your device for internal use to improve our app design and features. We do this ourselves and through third party providers, including Flurry Analytics, Google Analytics, and Facebook. 

### Aggregate Statistics

We may share aggregate statistics derived from log files and analytics. 

### How We Handle Personally-Identifying Information

MathPapa discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on MathPapa's behalf or to provide services available on MathPapa's website and mobile applications, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using MathPapa's website and mobile applications, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. MathPapa will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, MathPapa discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or when MathPapa believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of MathPapa or third parties, the public at large or if MathPapa is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. If you are a registered user of a MathPapa website or mobile application and have supplied your email address, MathPapa may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with MathPapa and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. 

### Cookies and Web Beacons

The Service does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

### DoubleClick Cookie

.:: Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to [www.mathpapa.com](https://www.mathpapa.com/). .:: Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to [www.mathpapa.com](https://www.mathpapa.com/) and/or other sites on the Internet. .:: Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). (Alternatively, users may opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).)

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense. 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on [www.mathpapa.com](https://www.mathpapa.com/) send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

MathPapa has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. MathPapa's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

### Third-Party Advertising

The Service may contain third-party advertising and information collected via such advertising shall be subject to the privacy policy of the advertising entity, including: 

  * Google DoubleClick: [Google's Privacy Policy ](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)
  * MoPub: [MoPub Privacy Policy ](http://www.mopub.com/legal/privacy/)
  * AdMob: [Google's Privacy Policy ](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)
  * Facebook: [Facebook's Privacy Policy ](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php)

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. MathPapa's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

### Payment Processing

The Service may use third-party payment processors, including Stripe. The third-party applications may collect certain financial information from you to process payments. 

### Opt-Out Requests

You can contact us to ask us whether we are keeping information about you; to provide you with access to any information we have about you; how your information is being used; update, correct, or delete your information, or opt-out of the collection and use of certain information by sending an email to contact@mathpapa.com or by writing us at MathPapa, 2627 Hanover Street, Palo Alto, CA 94304, specifying the nature and scope of your request. If you choose to delete your information or opt-out of the collection and use of your information, you understand that certain services may no longer be available to you, potentially including revocation of your account. Please state in your correspondence the details of your request. We may require proof of your identity before we provide you with the requested information. We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data erased, rectified, amended, or completed. Approved requests will be processed within ten (10) days of the date on which we receive the request. 

### Security

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. When you enter credit card information on our order forms, that information is encrypted and protected by our third-party payment providers. No method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

### Children's Privacy

We do not seek or knowingly collect any personal information about children under 13 years of age without parental consent. If we become aware that we have unknowingly collected personal information from a child under the age of 13 without parental consent, we will make commercially reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database. 

If you are the parent or guardian of a minor child who has provided us with personal information, you may contact us using the information below to request it be deleted. 

### Governing Law

This Privacy Policy shall be subject to the "Governing Law and Arbitration; No Class Actions" provision in the Terms and Conditions of Use. 

### Your California Privacy Rights

This Privacy Policy describes how we may share your information for marketing purposes. It applies to all MathPapa customers, including California residents. 

We share information with others as more fully set forth above. We share your information with other parts of our business and with our service providers. 

You may contact us with any questions, or to request a list of third parties to whom we may disclose information for marketing purposes and the categories of information we may disclose. See below for our contact information: 

### Contact Us

If you require any more information or have any questions or complaints about our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us by email at contact@mathpapa.com.
